现在我们可以访问云资产了,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Now that we have
access to the cloudinary assets,
我们来看看这几页吧。
let's jump into the pages.
我想在这个页面上放一张图片。
And I wanna pull up an image on this page.
所以我要从《盖茨比》中挖掘出 GraphQL。
So I'm going to get GraphQL out of gatsby.
然后我也想得到
And then I also wanna get
盖茨比形象。
image from gatsby-image.
因为这是一个页面组件，所以我打算使用页面查询。
And because this is a page component,
I'm just going to use a page query.
所以我可以导出一个常量，我称之为 query，使用 graphql。
So I can export a constant,
I'll call it query, use graphql.
我们也可以通过静态查询来实现这一点。
We could also do this with a static query.
这是一种偏好，因为我们知道图像是什么
It's kind of a preference thing at this
point because we know what the image is
会是。
gonna be.
我要设置一个查询，我要化名文件图像。
And I'm gonna set up a query, and
I'm gonna alias file to image.
所以我要做的是，我要开始，也许我会从这里开始
So what I'm doing is I'm gonna start
with maybe I'll start over here so
这样更容易看清楚。
it's a little easier to see.
我要建立一个文件查询和我想用的文件,
I'm gonna set up a file query and
the file that I wanna use,
我想找到匹配的名字。
I want to match the name.
我希望这个名字等同于底线。
And I want the name to
equal the grounding.
然后在这里面，我想得到儿童计量资产，流体。
And then inside of this, I want to
get the childCloudinaryAsset, fluid.
还有一种方便的模式
And then there's a a kind of
convenience pattern that we're
我一会儿给你们看。
gonna use that I'll show you in a second.
但是这个有点笨拙，而且不是很清楚我得到了什么。
But this is a little unwieldy, and
it's not super clear what I'm getting.
所以我要给这些起名字。
So I'm gonna alias these.
将这个名称更改为 image，将这个名称更改为 Cloudinary。
Change the name of this one to image,
and this one to Cloudinary.
你可以在这里看到文件 childCloudinaryAsset。
And you'll see here it's
file childCloudinaryAsset.
当我给它们赋予别名时，它们就是同样的数据。
When I've aliased them,
it's the same data.
但是现在这个物体又回来了。
But now the object comes
back with a little more.
对于我们如何使用它，它更具描述性。
It's a little more descriptive
about how we're using it.
所以这样就比较容易推理了。
So it's a little easier to reason about.
所以我要做图像处理。
So I'm gonna do image.
实际上，我可以把这个抄下来。
Actually, I can just copy this out.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 不需要名字。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Don't need a name.
所以我要摆脱它。
So I'm gonna get rid of that.
然后，它不工作的图形。
And then it doesn't work in graphical.
但是当你在 Gatsby 工作的时候，一些变压器插件会出口
But when you're working in Gatsby, some
of the transformer plugins will export
我们称之为 GraphQL 片段，这是一种方便的方式。
what's called a GraphQL fragment,
which is kind of a convenience way.
要封装所有的图像文件或
To wrap up all of the image file or
将你需要的图像字段简化为一个片段。
the image fields that you need
into a simplified fragment.
所以，这个工作原理是我们可以输入云 / 资产流体
So, the way that this works is we
can type in cloudinaryassetfluid and
它会扩展到所有的领域。
it will just expand into all the fields.
所以与其在这里说，我想要纵横比,
So instead of having to go in here and
say, I want the aspect ratio,
64，the sizes，the source，and the source set，i can instead just use
the base 64, the sizes, the source, and
the source set, I can instead just use
那个碎片，它会为我们扩展到所有的领域。
that fragment and it'll expand
to all of those fields for us.
这只是为了方便，不一定是必须的。
It's just for convenience,
not necessarily required.
如果我们愿意，我们可以走很长的路。
We could do it the long way if we wanted.
所以一旦我们编写了这个查询，它就会被注入到数据支持中。
So once we've written that query,
it's gonna get injected as a data prop.
然后我要添加一个图像字段,
And then I am going to add an image field,
这是盖茨比形象的组成部分，我们把液体
so this is the Gatsby image component and
we're just gonna stick the fluid
所以数据图像云流体
that we got into it, so
data image cloudinary fluid and
作为使用屏幕阅读器的用户的 alt 标签，我们会说
as an alt tag for people using
screen readers, we're gonna say
这是一个 Negroni，我总是在 alt 标签的末尾加上句号。
it's a Negroni, I always put
a period at the end of my alt tags.
我曾经读到有人用屏幕阅读器增加了一个停顿,
I read once from somebody who's using
a screen reader that that adds a pause,
而不是直接说下一个单词。
instead of just like
slamming into the next word.
我从来没有亲自验证过这一点，但我总是这样做。
I have never verified this myself,
but I've just always done it.
如果使用屏幕阅读器的人想纠正我,
If somebody who uses the screen
reader wants to correct me,
请在 Twitter 上找到我，让我知道这不是正确的做事方式。
please find me on Twitter and let me know
of that's not the right way to do things.
因此，我不认为我们需要重新启动，我认为它会正常工作。
So with this, I don't think we need
to restart, I think it'll just work.
所以我要拯救它，我们有我们的疑问,
So I'm gonna save it, we've got our query,
我们的查询来自他的数据，我们把它用在我们的盖茨比形象道具中,
our query is coming in his data,
we're using it in our Gatsby image prop,
如果我看了主页，就会发现我们做得很好。
and if I look at the homepage,
there we go great.
但这个问题太大了。
But this is too big.
好像我不想让这个毁了我的整个屏幕。
Like I don't want this
to bury my whole screen.
所以我要添加一些变换。
So instead I'm gonna add
some transformations.
我想把长宽比缩小一点。
I wanna make the aspect
ratio a little more narrow.
所以为了做到这一点，我可以跳入这个流体标签
So to do that,
I can just jump in to this fluid tag and
我可以说，添加一些转换，并且
I can say, add some transformations, and
我想要的变换是我想要一个长宽比，比如说18乘9。
the transformations that I want is I want
an aspect ratio of let's say 18 by 9.
有点狭窄，不过我觉得还不错。
So kind of narrow, but
I think that's good.
我们希望庄稼被填满而不是被压扁。
We want the crop to be
fill instead of squashing.
然后因为这个，在我做之前，让我给你们展示一下这个是什么样的。
And then because this, actually let me
show you how this looks before I do it.
所以，这是默认的裁剪，只是有点，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: So, this is
the default crop, it just kind of, right?
但是 Cloudinary 会把焦点放在图片的主题上,
But Cloudinary will do this thing where
it'll focus on the subject of an image,
感觉还不错。
which is kind of nice.
看看这个，如果我用 g。
So, check this out, if I run g.
它在哪里，g auto，我告诉它专注于这个主题。
Where is it, g auto and
I tell it to focus on the subject.
是引力的缩写，就像图像聚焦的地方。
G is short for gravity which is
like where the image is focused.
所以我有 g 自动，我集中在这个主题，然后我可以回到这里。
So I have got g auto and I'm focusing on
the subject and then I can come back here.
它并没有改变太多，只是稍微推动了一下。
And it doesn't change much but
it just nudges it a little bit.
如果你有人物的照片，那就更明显了
It's way more obvious if
you've got pictures of people
因为这样可以让他们的脸更清晰。
because it will pull
their faces into focus.
再次说明，真的很酷的 API，我们今天并没有对它做太多的工作，但是它确实很酷
Again really cool API we're not really
doing too much with it today but it's
这是一个很好的方法，可以在你的照片上省去很多麻烦。
a nice way to shortcut a lot of hassle
in your art direction on your photos.
现在我们已经知道了，我想再做一次。
So now that we've got this,
I want to do this one more time.
我想把它放进历史页面，让我们用一个不同的。
And I want to pull it into the the history
page and let's use a different one.
所以我要拿这个。
So I'm gonna grab this.
让我们从《了不起的盖茨比》中挖掘出一些故事
Let's get graphql out of gatsby and
那我们就从 getsby 的图像中找出图像。
then let's get image out of getsby image.
所以这个，我想用这个 Negroni-naff，所以
So this one,
I wanna use this Negroni-naff, so
我去拿那个。
I'm just gonna grab that one.
而这一个，我不需要任何改变，所以
And this one,
I don't need any transformation, so
我只是想摆脱他们。
I'm just gonna get rid of them.
然后在这里，我们得到了我们的数据
And then down here, we've got our data and
我可以直接从索引开始我们可以直接复制出来。
I can just go right over the index
We can copy that straight out.
所以现在当我点击历史记录时，我们得到了一张图片。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: So now when I click
through the history, we've got an image.
所以这是一个，我被放大了，这就是为什么它这么大。
So this is a, well I was zoomed way in,
that's why it was so big.
[笑声]现在我们有了一个简单的，好看的网站
[LAUGH] So now we've got a kind of
a a simple site with good looking
不会占用电脑太多空间的资产。
assets that aren't taking up
a ton of space on the computer.
我们可以看到，如果我们从源头看这些元素
And we can see if we look at
the elements at the the source
盖茨比形象所产生的影响。
that what Gatsby image is generating.
这是一个完整的饶舌歌手,
So this is the full rapper and
inside of it,
我们得到一个占位符，它占据了图像的纵横比大小
we get a placeholder that occupies
the aspect ratio size of the image
以防止内容在加载图像之前跳转。
to keep the content from
jumping before the image loads.
所以这是一件非常美好的事情。
So that's a really nice thing to have.
然后它有一个基64编码，小版本的图像。
Then it has a base 64 encoded,
small version of the image.
所以我们可以做这个淡入。
So that we can do this fade in.
这是一种被媒介推广的技术。
And this is a technique that
was popularized by medium.
这就是所谓的模糊技术。
It's called the blur up technique.
它的意思是，你取一个30像素宽的图像，然后
And what it means is you take a version of
the image that's like 30 pixels wide, and
然后你只要放大它和浏览器是有帮助的，因为它知道一个30
then you just blow it up and the browser
to be helpful because it knows that a 30
以650像素为单位显示的像素宽度看起来会像垃圾。
pixel wide shown in 650 pixels
is gonna look like garbage.
增加模糊效果。
Adds a blur.
所以我们不需要做什么特别的事情。
So we don't have to do anything special.
我们只是说嘿,
We just say like hey,
在浏览器中显示这么大的图片是个坏主意。
show this tiny image really big in
the browsers like that's a bad idea.
你不应该那样做。
You shouldn't do that.
我来帮你。
Let me help.
然后，一旦它在视口，在这种情况下,
Then, once it's in the viewport,
which in this case,
它总是在视窗，因为它载入在顶部。
it's always in the viewport
cuz it loads at the top.
盖茨比将以非阻塞的方式加载全尺寸图像
Gatsby will load the full size
image in a non blocking way so
页面将渲染，然后它去得到图像。
the page will render and
then it goes to get images.
当载入全尺寸图像时，它会淡入。
When the full size images loaded,
it fades in.
所以如果你用的是慢速连接,
So if you're on a slower connection,
你会发现这大大提高了加载页面的速度
you'll see that this drastically increases
the speed of loading the page and
并不影响画面的质量和美感。
doesn't take away from the quality or
the beauty of the images.
所以，有了这些，我认为我们可以挽救我们的工作，并且
So, with that,
I think we can save our work, and
然后我们再继续下一个话题。
then we'll move on to the next thing.